This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that I wanna take you to.
Let's head forth and.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
It's a dream come true.
Vito, what are you doing?
It's so good Get this, the
president of the W .E .J.
and Jeremy's boss are
talking right now Why
should I be surprised
that two guys are talking?
They got ears in their mouth, don't they?
Well, just saying, it's
a real VIP show, Lili.
The eldest son and the
minister of candy, Perospero.
The eldest daughter and the
minister of fruit, Kampote.
The second son, Sweet General Katakuri.
The 14th daughter, Sweet General Smoothie.
The third son, Daifugo.
And the fourth son, Oven.
It's a whole den of beasts in
there, I'm telling you, Lili.
Of course, when all of them were on
our side, that was swell, you know.
But now that they're gonna be our
enemies, it does make me worry a bit.
Huh? Enemies?
If you got time to think stupid
crap, go check downstairs.
Sure, father.
Let's move, Gabby.
From what I hear, the wedding
cake will be quite a sight to see.
Huh?
Mama, it's Mother Carmel.
Ah, splendid.
Today we're graced by our dear mother.
And she's smiling brightly
as always, isn't she?
Like a shining sun.
shedding its rays on your
daughter's wedding that's correct why
mother carmel is the light of the
world i have no idea who this lady is
you must excuse me this is the first
tea party i've been to i see that
you are very fond of this woman
here but how are you related exactly
These are my memories!
So keep your nose out of my business!
How's everything going?
The cooks finished prepping,
so they're off work.
They're celebrating with a banquet now.
We blocked all the passages
while they were distracted.
Nice job.
That should keep reinforcements from
coming up to the roof for a while.
Next, we'll set the horn transponder
snails to jam any signals.
Once this goes down, the
whole venue will be isolated.
Don't forget to set up for you-know-what.
Yes, sir.
Charlotte, we brought a little
gift to you and your daughter.
It's nothing special, but I have a
feeling it might be right up your alley.
Oh, I do love a good treasure chest.
You know me well, don't you?
Bet it's got something
lovely hidden inside.
I brought you a treasure
chest as well, Lin-Lin.
Congrats.
Please accept this one for me, too.
And I got you a rare treasure from
the south to give you a little hint.
My treasure comes from the farthest
reaches of the northern sea.
Everyone's so generous.
A whole mountain of treasure,
and it's all for me.
I just can't thank you enough.
This really is the perfect day.
Speaking of treasure chests, Mami-ga,
I heard you've landed a priceless
heirloom from deep undersea. Did you?
You have ears everywhere.
Though I'd expect nothing less, it's true.
A treasure passed down for generations.
A cherished symbol of undersea royalty.
No idea why Neptune let it go after
all these years, but it's mine now.
a legendary treasure here just for me
the tomate box i admit
it's rather steeply
never mind the box what's inside so have
you opened it yet i must know actually i've
been saving it for the big feast after
pudding's wedding i'll open it along with
all my other treasure
chests it's even more
fun if we can enjoy it together right Ha,
Father?
Vito, all wrapped up?
Everything is ready to go, little old.
All right, nice work.
Go ahead and get changed, boys.
Yes, sir!
Caesar, bring out the mirror.
Your name isn't Caesar, it's Gastino!
Ha!
So this is the entrance
to the tea party, is it?
Ha! Ah!
Laugh it up while you can, scum!
You'll get what's coming!
That's Caesar Cloth!
Like you ain't scum, too.
Anyway, go hide that mirror.
We're gonna need it in a sec.
Shut up! I know that!
When big mom starts
screaming, that's your cue.
Fly into the hall and
bring that mirror with you.
Easy Pass, right?
That's our only escape route,
so everyone's counting on you.
Needless to say, don't
get any funny ideas.
Don't think I'd wait till
now to betray you? Oh, no.
Veggie and his crew are up to something.
I took care of it.
If we suffer an information leak, this
whole thing goes down to drink, capisce?
We got 30 minutes to the big event.
Is Straw Hat and his little
crew ready to do this?
We better not be running
around like some kind of moron.
And why are you asking me?
The brat is inside your body, isn't he?
Eh.
Hey, you buffoons!
Why are you sleeping?
It's time to get ready!
Let them rest for now.
They've had quite a journey
since they've arrived.
I'll wake them up ten
minutes before we start.
I can't believe this crap.
You do what you want, but I'll ditch
them the second they get in my way.
Don't worry.
I'm watching the time.
I'll make sure everything is in order
This is a circus.
I can't believe him No kidding!
If you're done, you
better get back inside.
I'm about to walk into the venue myself.
I need everyone to be on guard.
Once we go through that door.
There's no turning back.
I hope you're ready to make this happen.
A lot's riding on you.
Thin smoke, Sanji!
You know, I wasn't planning on
getting married when I came out here.
So, it's kind of strange sitting
side by side with you like this.
I feel like I'm living in a dream.
Stay cool, stay cool.
Don't fall for her charms!
So is this...
A good dream?
Or a bad dream?
Holy crap, is she cute!
Well, it's a good dream, of course.
Oh, thank goodness. I was worried.
Get it together, you jackass.
She's just acting.
She's planning to shoot you dead.
Hold on a sec.
What if this is the real her and
what I saw before was a dream?
No, you idiot!
You're gonna get yourself killed.
You had it right before.
It's just ah
Oh, yeah, I
Was thinking about our kiss.
I thought you might be shy doing
it in front of all the people here.
I
could just kiss you on
the forehead if you want.
Ahh!
What was that?
Why is the group falling from
the ceiling in a time like this?
Where did all this blood come from?
He's out cold.
Sanji, no!
Please wake up!
What the hell is wrong
with this little freak?
I can't wait to shoot him.
Everything going well, yeah?
Haven't noticed anything
that's what I like to hear.
Today's wedding has to go off without a
lickety hitch—in other words, stay vigilant!
vigilant
Yeah, I got it.
12 o 'clock!
It's 12 o 'clock!
Ladies and gentlemen, may
I have your attention.
Our main event's here at last.
The 35th daughter of Big Mom's
family, Charlotte Pudding,
And the third prince of the
German kingdom, Vince Smoke Sanji,
will join their hands in marriage.
Let's party!
Spirit!
Spirit! Spirit!
Ha, ha, ha! Awesome!
Without further ado, I now
present the Bride and Groove!
A pirate crew led by
the Emperor Big Mom and
the notorious evil army
Chairman Double Six.
This young couple will
bring the two notorious
families together in a deadly alliance.
Let the strength of their bond give
rise to a brand new flower of evil.
Blooming madly in this world.
Give them a hand.
What a dove?
Their future's so bright
it'll scorch your eyeballs!
So let's hear it for the happy couple!
That nitwit!
He's really selling this!
The wedding begins, but
whose blood will be shed?
Wake up!
Luffy!
The wedding is starting right now. Luffy!
So much meat.
Wake up!
Damn it!
Sanji is counting on you!
Hey, is there a secret to this?
Well, let's see.
He was running around a
bunch and fell asleep,
and now he's having food
dreams, so he must be hungry.
Hey, do you have any meat?
That should wake him up. Meat?
We don't have time for
breakfast right now.
Little do you know, this is your Requiem.
That's right, just sit there like human
garbage with that stupid look on your face.
Oh, Sanji, I'm so happy.
I think, maybe, this was meant to be.
Pudding, you're right.
I think so, too.
Keep your wits about you, Sanji.
This isn't a game.
If you lose focus now,
she's gonna kill you!
Merit!
Merit! Merit!
I had a taste of love and sorrow too.
I found love and I was
hurt, but I never lost hope.
And now I'll leave the gold.
Count the iron.
Even if.
Rain pours down.
Danger comes.
Stay close, never let go.
And let your passion grow.
A symbol of your mom.
When in the day.
Thank you.
It's good for a king.
No, a kingdom.
Yummy.
This cake is worthy of
a double-pate strength.
Splendid work, Struzan.
Why, I simply can't praise you enough.
Just doing my duty, Mama.
I can't wait to try it.
Oh, look, this lovely cake.
It's going to be our altar.
You're lovely, my dear.
No, stop.
Gosh, you are so silly.
And so did.
Oh, Pudding, so cute.
She looks just like me
when I was that age.
And how long ago was that?
Well, someone has a death wish.
No!
My, my, my, my.
Enjoy it while it lasts,
my hapless little friends, because
soon it will all come crashing down.
We're nearly at the climax.
Here, please enjoy the
wedding from these VIP seats.
Yes, you'll want a
front row view for this.
Your own execution.
Let the moon and the bride and groom kiss.
Our bloody banquet will begin.
Sorry, Vince, folks, but you gotta go.
Finally.
Old Sanji really lucked out, didn't he?
If I'd have known pudding was that
hot, I would have married her myself.
Marry Big Mom's daughter?
No thanks.
Sanji's nothing but a sacrifice.
Remember that.
Once he's married, he'll be under Big
Mom's thumb for the rest of his life.
Hard pass.
That's the last thing I'd want.
I see.
We're surrounded by the
strongest Charlotte siblings.
Rather easy targets, aren't we?
And sitting ducks since we're unarmed.
That's fine.
The world is better off without Germa.
Well, most of us at least.
You have to escape Sanji.
You have a plan, right?
But can I trust Captain Luffy?
I want to do you, Sanji—take pudding
to be your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold in
sickness and in health,
for richer or for poorer,
till death do you part!
part
Hey guys, hurry!
We're gonna be late!
That's your fault!
Don't complain to us!
Do you plan to remain loyal and
to love and cherish each other?
I can hardly believe
it's all coming together.
What's wrong, Pudding?
Why are you collapsing?
Now, you may lift the
veil and kiss the bride.
Katakuri, what's wrong?
You saw the future, didn't you?
This is it. You ready?
Yes.
Thank you.
Take a good look, Sanji.
Let's see how you feel
when you see my hideous.
third eye.
Good boy.
Stay just like that.
To think that you were
hiding such a beautiful eye.
Sorry, I, uh, no, I shouldn't stare.
It's just so pretty.
What's she doing?
Shoot him, Pudding.
Are you okay?
You idiot.
What are you saying?
Then, when the happy couple appears,
we'll see Sanji, the man of the hour.
Suddenly, much to his shock and horror, he
will discover that you have a third eye.
He expected a beautiful face,
but now he sees his bride for
the monster that she truly is.
He'll be paralyzed with shock.
Screw you.
Why are you doing this?
I've never heard those
words once in my life.
You're just lying to me, aren't you?
No one would ever think
this eye is beautiful.
There's something wrong with you.
What is going on, Pudding?
Kill him already.
No one has ever.
You're my daughter, but that
eye still creeps me out.
Cover it with your bangs, would you?
Yes, ma 'am. I will.
What's that eye?
It's really creeping
me out, little monster.
It's Rose, you're a weirdo!
Please stop!
Leave me alone!
There, that's much better.
Little freak, little freak.
That's it.
I've had enough.
Bastards, bastards.
I'll murder all of you. Get away.
Pudding?
You go to hell!
Is this pity? Dammit!
Pastor, it's beautiful!
How dare you tell me that!
Are you gonna do this or not, Pudding?
What's wrong? Talk to me.
Priest, he'll do it!
That's no use. He'll miss.
He dodged.
Don't let me down, Straw Hat.
Luffy, that's your cue. Go! Right! Ready!
Was that a gunshot?
The priest did it—no, he got shot. Why?
What is going on here?
Could it be why
the hell didn't pudding shoot him?
Katakuri, tell me what you see.
We have a bigger problem,
mama—something completely unexpected.
Even I can't stop this. What now?
We fight or are we waiting?
we waiting So is this something new?
Almost there!
Please forgive me, Mama.
I had no choice but to do what they said.
It's time to take Sanji back!
What now?
I can't stop them.
They're going to pop out of the cake.
What?
Let's go!
I didn't know!
Oh my God!